Ivy City-Trinidad Citizens Association 020
People's Archive, MLK Library
Ivy City-Trinidad Citizens Association Records
1966-1983
People's Archive, MLK Library
Ivy City-Trinidad Citizens Association
020
1 Boxes
0.5 Linear feet
Arrangement
Processed without series.
Biographical / Historical
The Ivy City-Trinidad Citizens Association was originally incorporated as an Ivy City neighborhood focused association in 1911, and added the Trinidad neighborhood in 1953 to its charter. The Association promotes improvement of government services and mutual interests of the residents of the Ivy City-Trinidad neighborhood. Its jurisdiction is bounded by New York Avenue NE, Florida Avenue NE, and Bladensburg Road NE.
Custodial History
Unknown donor.
Scope and Contents
Records include the Ivy City-Trinidad Citizens Association's minutes from 1966-1967, a constitution, and other materials collected by the Association.
Neighborhoods; Citizens' Associations; Associations, institutions, etc; Ivy City (Washington, D.C.); Organizational Records; Minutes (Records)
- Series 1
  - Notebook minutes, 1966-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Notebook minutes, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, May-Sept. 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, Nov. 1976 - March 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, April 1978 - January 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, March 1979 - January 1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, February 1980 - January 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, January - September 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, November 1983 - September 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, September 1986 - February 1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assorted Minutes, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Community Association Constitution, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Federation of Civic Association, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Notice of Interest, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - City Council materials, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)